



Mohammad Fahad

Full Stack Web Developer & UI Designer.

- Ohaka-Bangladesh.
- ▼ fahadwebdesigner6@gmail.com
- **U** 01858281093

SOCIAL

Bē Behance

in Linkedin

Facebook

PROFILE

I am a Full Stack Web Developer & UI Designer. I'm very passionate and dedicated to my work. With 2 years experience as a professional Web developer, I have acquired the skills and knowledge necessary to make your project a success. I've helped so many organizations improve their online presence and hope I can help you to make an awesome website for your business. I am passionate to learn more and get my skill sets more polished and learn new technologies. I love programming and coding as It's my passion.

EDUCATION

MASTER OF GRAPHICS DESIGN.

Institute of Shikhbe Shobai

2020 - 2021

MASTER IN WEB DEVELOPER.

Institute of Shikhbe Shobai

2021 - 2022

MASTER IN SHOPIFY DEVELOPER.

Institute of Shikhbe Shobai 2022 - 2023

SKILLS

- HTML
- Wordpress
- CSS
- Shopify
- Bootstrap
- Elementor
- Basic Javascript
 Pagefly
- Jquery
- Shogun

EXPERIENCE

C

MASTER OF GRAPHICS DESIGN

From 2020 to 2021

work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds, delivering the best results for the company and improving productivity.

MASTER OF FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

From 2021 to 2022

work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds, delivering the best results for the company and improving productivity.

MASTER OF SHOPIFY DEVELOPER

From 2022 to 2023

work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds, delivering the best results for the company and improving productivity.

CERTIFICATES

Certified for compliance in the course.

Graphics & UI Design. (2020)

Certified for compliance in the course.

Full Stack Web Development. (2020)

Certified for compliance in the course.

Shopify Development. (2020)

REFERENCES

ICT Teacher

Bikrom Aditto

phone: +880-000-000-0000 email:user@gmail.com

ICT Teacher

Bikrom Aditto

phone: +880-000-000-0000 email:user@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

- English
- Bengali
- Arabic
- Hindi

INTERESTS







